airtickets24.com 2017-10-04

# Privacy policy - www.airtickets24.com

At Airtickets24.com we understand that data privacy is a very important issue. Airtickets24.com is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal details every time you make a purchase online, and considers the safety of customer information a matter of great importance. This policy explains how we use customer information and how we protect your privacy. Please read it carefully. By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

### What kind of information we collect

**In general.** We receive and collect any kind of information you provide us. This includes information that can identify you ("Personal Information"), including name and surname, telephone number and your email. We also collect information about the transactions you complete including your credit card number, name of the card holder and expiration date. We may collect additional information regarding your travel preferences, including meal or seat requests as well as the frequent flyer/hotel/car rental program information. You can choose not to provide information to us, however, please be aware that some information is necessary to complete an order, manage your bookings or even to take part in contests or surveys. Therefore without providing it you might be unable to perform your desired action. 

**Passenger information.** When you make a purchase through Airtickets24.com, we collect your travel preferences. Your profile is updated and enriched every time you use Airtickets24.com. 

**Automatic collection of information.** We automatically collect certain information about your computer when you visit Airtickets24.com. For example, we collect information regarding the browser you use (eg. Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, etc.) and IP address. We may also collect information about your activity on our site, including information such as trips viewed and purchases made. The main goal of collecting this automatic information is to improve user experience on our site. 

**Cookies.** When you visit Airtickets24.com, we store cookies in your computer. Cookies are small pieces of anonymous text data, stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. They enable Airtickets24.com to provide features and remember your preferences based on your last visit. Note that all information contained in cookies is encrypted for security reasons. You can always choose not to receive cookies from Airtickets24.com, but in this case you might not be able to access and use some of the site's features or complete a purchase successfully. 

### How we use your information

Personal data such as the name of the card holder, credit card number, expiry date and CVV are required to complete the booking process through our site. This data could also be used for any additional services you might require to purchase after your booking has been completed (i.e. change the dates of your travel); for this reason we use tokenization and vault services provided by banks or equally rated in terms of security (PCI) specialized third parties in order to ensure safe transmission of your card details. It is important to note that e-Travel and/or any e-Travel employee will at no case store or have direct access to your credit card information. Furthermore, no additional charge will ever be processed without your consent.

Your anonymized information (other than payment information) might be used to improve and personalize our services.

In case you opted in to receive our newsletters we may use your information to send you offers and news about Airtickets24.com products and services or those of other carefully selected companies which we think that they may be of interest to you.

### Sharing your information

Airtickets24.com may share your information with the following entities: 

  * Suppliers, such as hotels, airlines, ferry companies, insurance providers and car rental agencies who offer the final service concerning the reservations performed through our Website. We do not share your email address with these suppliers unless they need it to complete your booking or in case a problem occurs. Generally the information provided to suppliers is limited to the required extent for a successfully completed booking. These suppliers may also contact you if necessary, to obtain additional information or to facilitate the process of your travel reservation. 
  * Business units that are affiliates of e-Travel S.A. which owns Airtickets24.com. The affiliate sites [Avion.ro](http://www.avion.ro/), [Fantasticgreece.com](http://www.fantasticgreece.com/), [Pamediakopes.gr](http://www.pamediakopes.gr/), [Trip.bg](http://www.trip.bg/), [Trip.ru](http://www.trip.ru/), [Trip.ua](http://www.trip.ua/), [Mytrip.com](http://www.mytrip.com/), [Trip.kz](http://www.trip.kz/), [Trip.ae](http://www.trip.ae/), [Logotypon.com](http://www.logotypon.com/), [design by Grel.gr](http://www.grel.gr/) have access to your information and may also send you details of other products and services which we consider of your interest. These companies follow the same privacy policy as the one presented here. 
  * We may also share anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of users on our Website, or the most popular holiday destinations searched or booked by our users. This information does not contain any personal information and is used for research purposes only. 

### How we protect your information

We take all the necessary security measures to protect your personal data against unauthorized access and/or alteration, disclosure and destruction. We use all the necessary administrative, technical and physical security measures to protect the personal information you provide us. For example, only authorized employees may access your personal information. In addition, we use encryption during the transmission of your personal information across the internet as well as firewalls and intrusion detection systems to prevent unauthorized access to your personal information. 

### Children's privacy

Airtickets24.com does not sell travel or other services to children. If a child under 18 years old attempts to make a purchase through Airtickets24.com, we will use his/her personal information only to inform the child that we need parental permission to complete the reservation. 

### External links

Airtickets24.com may contain links to other Websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. 

### Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact our Customer Support service at +1 (917) 2849583.
